(Sheldon:)how dismissive I've been
of your contributions.
(Howard:)I appreciate that.
And I just hope
(Sheldon:)that this scholarship
can rescue your child
(Sheldon:)from the subpar education
(Sheldon:)and menial life
of an engineer.
(Leonard:)Sheldon.
What?
(Sheldon:)I didn't sign it yet.
(Raj:)I hear what you're saying,
(Raj:)but I've known Emily
a long time,
(Raj:)and I think she deserves
the benefit of the doubt.
(Claire:)All right, it's your life.
(Claire:)But you know
how this is gonna end.
(Raj:)As a matter of fact, I do.
(Raj:)I'm gonna comfort her,
because I'm a caring
(Raj:)and decent friend
who's happy to be there
(Raj:)when she needs someone
to talk to.
(Raj:)Good talk.